A JetBlue Airlines flight from West Palm Beach to New York City was forced to turn
around and land Sunday morning after the plane struck a
around and land Sunday morning after the plane struck a bird.
A JetBlue Airlines flight from West Palm Beach to New York City was forced to turn
The flight from Palm Beach International Airport to LaGuardia Airport turned around
just minutes after takeoff following the strike.
No injuries were reported on the plane and the flight took off once again seven and
a half hours after the first attempt.
a hours after the first attempt.
No injuries were reported on the plane and the flight took off once again seven and
a half hours after the first attempt.
was like a split second of panic that resulted in this nervous reaction on the
plane, said passenger Brian Healy.
It was like a split second of panic that resulted in this nervous reaction on the
There was total quiet and then there was relief when the plane came to a stop.
email from JetBlue read,
team is working to accommodate customers on later flights.
was total quiet and then there was relief when the plane came to a stop.
An email from JetBlue read,
Our team is working to accommodate customers on later flights.